<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Moments</string>
    <string name="action_calendar">Calendar</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="home_screen">Home screen</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="seznam">List</string>
    <string name="home_screen_title">Take a moment for your health. This application gives you guidelines on how to drink Donat Mg natural mineral water, which have served as the basis for Rogaška Medical Centre therapies for more than a century. From now on, these guidelines are available to you, too.</string>
    <string name="drinking">Method of drinking</string>
    <string name="interval">Duration</string>
    <string name="start_date">Selected starting date for drinking:</string>
    <string name="button_indication_start">TURN ON</string>
    <string name="button_indication_stop">TURN OFF</string>
    <string name="confirmation_title">You have successfully set a reminder</string>
    <string name="confirmation_desc">A reminder to drink Donat Mg is now set. To your health!</string>
    <string name="confirmation_back">Back to entry page</string>
    <string name="save">SAVE</string>
    <string name="zbujanje">Waking up</string>
    <string name="zajtrk">Breakfast</string>
    <string name="kosilo">Lunch</string>
    <string name="vecerja">Dinner</string>
    <string name="spanje">Bed time</string>
    <string name="obrokov">Number of meals</string>
    <string name="close">CLOSE</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="licence">© Droga Kolinska d.d. All rights reserved. Droga Kolinska is part of the Atlantic Group.</string>
    <string name="rules">Terms and conditions of use</string>
    <string name="rules_title">General terms and conditions of use for the Moments mobile application</string>
    <string name="rules_title_desc">These General terms and conditions of use for the Moments mobile application (hereinafter: General Conditions) set the conditions and user instructions for the use of the mobile application. 
\n\nThe Moments mobile application (hereinafter: the Mobile Application) enables users to: 
\nget directions on drinking Donat Mg natural mineral water and 
\nset a Donat Mg drinking reminder based on the (health) issue selected, e.g. constipation, heartburn, magnesium deficiency, diabetes, gall bladder and pancreas disease, urinary tract stone formation, obesity and dieting, cardiovascular diseases, stress and headaches, and to increase the feeling of well-being.
\n\nUsers can search for the Mobile Application in mobile marketplaces where it is published (such as Google Play, Apple Store, etc.) and install it on their smartphones in the manner and under the conditions set by the provider of the respective mobile marketplace. 
\n\nThe Mobile Application provider is Droga Kolinska, d.d., Kolinska ulica 1, 1000 Ljubljana, Slovenia (hereinafter: the Provider).
\n\nThe User is any person who installs the Mobile Application on their mobile device.
\n\n<b>Conditions of use of the Mobile Application</b>
\nIt shall be deemed that, by installing the Mobile Application on the mobile device and using it, the User acknowledges and agrees with the General Conditions.
\n\n<b>Mobile application contents</b>
\nThe contents and information obtained by the user in the Mobile Application are exclusively of an informative nature and serve as an informative tool. They do not represent and may in no way take precedence over a doctor’s diagnosis, clinical consultation or the treatment itself. For any further information, or when in doubt, we recommend you consult your doctor and/or write to: info@donatmg.eu.
\nThe Mobile Application uses directions for drinking courses of treatment published at http://www.rogaska-medical.com/, through which the Mobile Application recommends an appropriate quantity and mode for drinking Donat Mg based on the various indicative states of an individual. The Provider shall not be responsible for improper use of the Mobile Application (e.g. the selection of the wrong indication, incorrect settings of daily rhythm, etc.) 
\nThe Provider is unable to guarantee total satisfaction for the advice obtained by the User while using the application and shall not undertake any responsibility for using the advice.
\n\n<b>Mobile application price</b>
\nThe Mobile Application is available to Users free of charge. The User shall pay for data transfer charged by their telecommunication services provider in accordance with the current price list of the provider.
\n\n<b>Privacy and the protection of personal data of the User</b>
\nIn the course of making the Mobile Application available for use by Users, the Provider shall not acquire, collect or otherwise process their personal data. 
\n\n<b>Copyright</b>
\nBy installing the Mobile Application on a mobile device, the User acquires a non-transferable and non-exclusive licence for the use of the Mobile Application exclusively on their mobile device for personal (non-commercial) use and in the manner and to the extent defined in these General Conditions. 
The Provider shall not transfer to the User any copyright or other industrial property right in respect and in connection with the Mobile Application (including, but not limited to, the right to use the trademark, logo, name, etc.)
\n\nThe User is particularly not allowed to:
<ul>
\n<li>make copies of the Mobile Application,</li>
\n<li>install the Mobile Application on a server or another platform,</li>
\n<li>distribute the Mobile Application in any way or enable network access to the Mobile Application,</li>
\n<li>rent the Mobile Application or grant sublicenses for the use of the Mobile Application,</li>
\n<li>translate, adapt, edit or otherwise remake the Mobile Application.</li>
</ul>
\n\nThe limitations of rights defined in this chapter shall not limit the rights of the User, in accordance with the Copyright and Related Rights Act (Official Gazette RS, No. 16/2007 – ZASP - UPB3 and 68/2008), and consumer protection legislation if the User has the status of a consumer in accordance with the aforementioned legislation.
\n\n<b>Limitation and exclusion of liability of the Provider</b>
\nThe User acknowledges and accepts that:
<ul>
\n<li>the data and contents obtained by the User via the Mobile Application is of an informative nature and does not represent, substitute or support a diagnosis of a medical condition, nor does it replace treatment. The Provider suggests that the User contact authorised institutions, service providers or pharmacies with regards to medical and other recommendations and instructions;</li> 
\n<li>The User shall be entirely responsible for all the data submitted in order to install and use the Mobile Application and that the Provider shall not under any circumstances be responsible for any consequences suffered by the User;</li>
\n<li>The Provider shall not accept any obligation or responsibility for factual defects or any other deficiencies of the Mobile Application and legal errors;</li>
\n<li>The Provider cannot guarantee that the Mobile Application fulfils all the requirements of the Users;</li>
\n<li>The Provider cannot guarantee the functioning of the Mobile Application and shall not accept any obligation or responsibility in the event of network failures, power cuts or other technical disruptions which could temporarily interrupt the smooth functioning of the Mobile Application and that the Provider shall not be responsible in cases of force majeure;</li>
\n<li>The Provider shall not be responsible for the functioning of the Mobile Application if the User has not fulfilled the technical and other conditions for the use of the Mobile Application;</li>
\n<li>The User shall be fully responsible for appropriate protection of all data stored on media (e.g. hard disks, smartphones, tablet computers, etc.) and that the Provider shall not be responsible for any damages sustained in the event that this data is lost;</li>
\n<li>The Provider does not guarantee the faultless and uninterrupted functioning of the Mobile Application, nor the absence of any malicious or dangerous programming code;</li>
\n<li>The Provider does not guarantee the functioning of the Mobile Application on all platforms and in combination with all hardware and software; </li>
\n<li>The Provider does not accept any obligation or responsibility in regards to the reliability and quality of the connection of the Mobile Application with the Internet or the reliability and quality of transfers via the Internet or any other communication channel.</li>
</ul>
\n\n<b>The Provider’s liability for damages</b>
\nThe Provider’s liability for damages for slight negligence shall be excluded to the widest extent permitted by the applicable legislation. 
\n\nThe Provider shall not be responsible for any loss of income, loss of data or any other consequential and indirect damages. 
\n\nThe Provider shall not be responsible for damages caused by non-performance of the Provider’s obligations in the event of force majeure. 
\n\n<b>Complaints</b>
\nThe Provider shall be responsible for solving complaints in regards to the functioning of the Mobile Application. The Provider shall solve complaints in accordance with its own rules which are made available to Users at the following web address:
www.donatmg.eu
\nE-mail contact of the Provider for resolving complaints is: info@donatmg.eu.
\nIf a complaint relates to the functioning of a telecommunication network and a payment for the services of an individual provider of telecommunication services, the User is obliged to provide all necessary documents to an appropriate department of the telecommunication service provider. Telecommunication service providers resolve complaints in accordance with their own general conditions for the provision of telecommunication services. 
\n\n<b>Termination of provision or use of the Mobile Application</b>
\nThe Mobile Application is available to Users as of 10/6/2014. The Provider may at any time terminate provision of the Mobile Application by informing Users in an appropriate manner (e.g. through a publication on its website wwww.donatmg.eu).
\n\nThe User has the right to stop using the Mobile Application at any time. This is done by removing the Mobile Application from their mobile device.
\n\nThe Provider has the right to disable access or prevent use of the Mobile Application without prior warning for any User violating these General Conditions.
\nIf the provision or use of the Mobile Application is terminated in accordance with this chapter, the right of the User to use the Mobile Application as defined by these General Conditions automatically ceases, and the User shall further be obliged to immediately stop using the Mobile Application and to destroy or delete all copies of the Mobile Application.
\n\n<b>Final provisions</b>
\nThe Provider has the right to publish a new version of the Mobile Application for technical or functional upgrades to the Mobile Application. The User will be informed of the new version of the Mobile Application through either the Mobile Application itself or an automatic update of the Mobile Application on the mobile device (depending on the User’s settings).  These General Conditions shall apply for any future upgrades or new versions or any other changes to the Mobile Application unless specifically defined otherwise by the Provider in each individual case. 
\n\nIn the event of unauthorised use of the Mobile Application or any other abuse of access or use of the Mobile Application the Provider has the right to implement all measures and other acts which, in accordance with its business judgement, it deems necessary for the protection of their rights and interests and/or those of any other person (e.g. preventing access to the Mobile Application).
\n\nThe Provider may at any time change these General Conditions. The Provider will in appropriate manner (e.g. through a publication on its website wwww.donatmg.eu) inform Users of the change to these General Conditions. 
\n\nAny User that does not agree with the change to the General Conditions must immediately stop using the Mobile Application. If the User continues to use the Mobile Application it shall be deemed that he/she agrees with the change to the General Conditions. 
\n\nThese General Conditions shall enter into force on the day of the publication of the application.
\n\nThese General Conditions are originally drawn up in the Slovenian language and adapted for users of English, Italian, Russian and Serbian versions. The Mobile Application can be used in the following languages: English, Italian, Russian and Serbian.
\n\nThe settling of disputes which may arise in connection with the Mobile Application and/or these General Conditions shall fall within the jurisdiction of Ljubljana Court in the Republic of Slovenia. The use of Slovenian law shall be agreed upon.
\n\nIn Ljubljana, 10/6/2014
</string>
    <string name="rules_subtitle">Podnaslov</string>
    <string name="rules_subtitle_desc">Pravila in pogoji uporabe. Pravila in pogoji uporabe. Pravila in pogoji uporabe. Pravila in pogoji uporabe. Pravila in pogoji uporabe</string>
  
    
    <string name="choose_language">Izberi jezik</string>
    <string-array name="languages">
        <item>English</item>
        <item>Pусский</item>
        <item>Hrvatski</item>
        <item>Italiano</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string name="choose_obrokov">Number of meals</string>
    <string-array name="obrokov">
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string name="indication_1">Constipation</string>
    <string name="indication_2">Heartburn</string>
    <string name="indication_3">Magnesium deficiency</string>
    <string name="indication_4">Diabetes</string>
    <string name="indication_5">Diseases of the gallbladder and pancreas</string>
    <string name="indication_6">Formation of urinary stones</string>
    <string name="indication_7">Obesity and losing weight</string>
    <string name="indication_8">Cardiovascular diseases</string>
    <string name="indication_9">Stress and headaches</string>
    <string name="indication_10">To feel better</string>

    <string name="indication_1_desc">Donat Mg is a natural osmotic laxative. It contains sulphate salts and about 1000 mg/l of magnesium. Sulphate ions have a considerable ability to bond with water, which increases the volume of intestinal content by 3 to 5 times, triggering intestinal peristalsis.</string>
    <string name="indication_2_desc">Thanks to its approximately 7800 mg of hydrogen carbonate, Donat Mg has a great capacity for bonding with acids and buffering free acids. With its alkaline effect, the sodium hydrogen carbonate in Donat Mg has an anti-inflammatory effect on the stomach lining. Furthermore, the magnesium and calcium found alongside the sodium reduce the swelling of the stomach lining.</string>
    <string name="indication_3_desc">Donat Mg is richer in magnesium than any other natural mineral water.* The recommended daily intake of this mineral is about 375 mg. An increased need for magnesium occurs during pregnancy and nursing as well as during the period of fast growth in adolescence. A greater lack of magnesium and, consequently, its increased need occur in elderly people, in people with metabolic disorders, in people taking certain medicines or following diets and in stressful periods. The best way to take magnesium is by drinking water. The magnesium in mineral water is immediately available to the body and is able to quickly participate in metabolic processes.\n\n*The examined comparative results include all recognised natural mineral waters available on the market and registered in the EU.</string>
    <string name="indication_4_desc">A magnesium deficiency in people with type 2 diabetes occurs due to the increased loss of magnesium through urine. All patients (including pregnant women) affected by diabetes mellitus for the first time suffer from blood sugar imbalances and an improper functioning of insulin. By drinking Donat Mg, it is possible to compensate the magnesium and better manage the disease, reducing the oscillations in blood sugar levels. </string>
    <string name="indication_5_desc">The bile of those whose stones have been surgically removed contains too much cholesterol or too few bile acids and lecithin. The bile that accumulates in the gallbladder is thicker, making it impossible for the gallbladder to empty completely. The magnesium sulphate in Donat Mg speeds up bile secretion. Regular evacuation of the gallbladder thus prevents the formation of gall stones.</string>
    <string name="indication_6_desc">Thanks to its high levels of hydrogen carbonate and magnesium, Donat Mg prevents the formation of calcium oxalate stones, uric acid stones and cystine stones, which thrives in an acidic environment, in a natural way. Both substances have an impact on the acid-base balance of the body. Hydrogen carbonate has an especially strong basic effect, since it bonds with acids and thus creates an alkaline environment that prevents the formation of these stones.</string>
    <string name="indication_7_desc">When on a diet, Donat Mg neutralises acids and replaces the lost minerals. It is very beneficial when we begin losing weight because it is a natural laxative and cleanses the body of toxins. The sulphate salts found in Donat Mg increase the secretion of cholecystokinin, which reduces appetite. Magnesium speeds up the metabolism, boosts immunity and increases energy reserves.</string>
    <string name="indication_8_desc">Donat Mg contains very little table salt and has consequently no effects on blood pressure. On the other hand, it contains high levels of magnesium (1000 mg/l). Magnesium is an essential element that, among other things, regulates the entire muscular system. Our heart is also a muscle that needs magnesium for its normal functioning. In order to prevent heart failure, arrhythmia and other disturbances that may be a consequence of magnesium deficiency, this important mineral has to be consumed on a daily basis.</string>
    <string name="indication_9_desc">Stress affects our psychological and physical health as the body loses more minerals through water. Consequently, the need for vitamins and minerals increases in stressful periods. Magnesium deficiency may even trigger certain types of headaches. Donat Mg is rich in this mineral, which is also called the anti-stress mineral and a salve for the nerves and muscles by the scientist.</string>
    <string name="indication_10_desc">Donat Mg is particularly rich in magnesium, sulphates and hydrogen carbonates, but also contains calcium, sodium and other microelements. It supplies our body with minerals and, thanks to its high levels of hydrogen carbonate, regulates the acid-base balance in the body. It can be consumed throughout one’s whole life to stay healthy and feel good.</string>
    
    <string name="drinking_na_tesce">On an empty stomach</string>
    <string name="drinking_pred_spanjem">Before bed</string>
    <string name="drinking_veckrat_dnevno">Several times a day</string>
    <string name="drinking_20_min_pred">20 min before meals</string>
    <string name="drinking_med_obroki">During meals and 1 to 2 hours after meals</string>
    <string name="drinking_opoldne">At noon</string>
    <string name="drinking_zvecer">In the evening</string>
    <string name="drinking_pred_kosilom">Before lunch</string>
    <string name="drinking_pred_vecerjo">Before dinner</string>
    <string name="drinking_obcutek_lakote">When hunger arises during and before meals</string>
    <string name="drinking_3_4_dnevno">3-4 times daily</string>
    <string name="drinking_pred_jedjo">Before meals</string>
    
    <string name="temperature_toplo">30–37 °C</string>
    <string name="temperature_mlacno">23–25 °C</string>
    <string name="temperature_sobna">20 °C</string>
    <string name="temperature_hladno">17–18 °C</string>
    <string name="volume_suffix">dcl</string>
  
    <string name="spped_hitro">Quickly</string>
    <string name="spped_razmeroma_hitro">Relatively quickly</string>
    <string name="spped_pocasi">Slowly</string>

    <string name="interval_stalno">Continuously or with shorter breaks</string>
    <string name="interval_5_dni">5 days, 2-day break, continuously</string>
    <string name="interval_6_tednov">6 weeks, 4-week break, 3 times a year</string>
    <string name="interval_3_mesece">3 months, 1-month break, 3 times a year</string>
    <string name="interval_2_meseca">2 months, 1-month break, 3 times a year</string>
        
    
</resources>
